Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/hanhnm219 (LinkedIn) www.behance.net/hanhnm (Portfolio) dribbble.com/hanhnm (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Artificial Intelligence for Design
User Experience Design
Team Leadership

Languages

Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Leading People and Teams Specialization

Google UX Design Professional Al For Business Specialization

Stay Competitive Using Design Thinking

Google Project Management Profestional

Nguyen Minh Hanh

UI/UX Manager

Hanoi Capital Region

Summary

Experienced 15 years in Graphic designer and 10 years in UI/UX Designer and 6 years as a UI/UX Design leader of working history in Agency and Technology Company. Participated in many big projects in the fields of Finance and Banking (Insbank, PVCOMbank, PVBank), Technology (VNPT, Viettel, mTouche), Tourism (KTO, Vietnam Airlines), Real Estate (Vinhome) and more...

Have good Leadership skills, UI/UX and Graphic Design. Graduated from the National University of Ho Chi Minh City, majoring in design and fine arts.

Experience

iCheck Corporation
UI/UX Design Manager
October 2020 - Present (4 years 6 months)
Hanoi, Vietnam

Keyframe Multimedia School
UI/UX Design Lecturer
June 2022 - Present (2 years 10 months)
Hanoi, Vietnam

MRD

UI/UX Design Project
May 2023 - November 2024 (1 year 7 months)

VNOKRs - JOHN Academy Head Of Design March 2020 - May 2023 (3 years 3 months) Vietnam

SEONGON
Design Manager

June 2018 - October 2020 (2 years 5 months)

Hanoi

CENTECH

Senior UI/UX Designer June 2015 - June 2018 (3 years 1 month)

Hanoi

mTouche Hanoi UI/UX Designer February 2013 - June 2015 (2 years 5 months) Hanoi

Diamond Media Graphic & UI/UX Designer November 2009 - February 2013 (3 years 4 months) Hanoi

GDC Media Graphic Designer July 2007 - November 2009 (2 years 5 months) Hanoi

Tan Ngoc Viet JSC Graphic Designer & Photographer July 2005 - July 2007 (2 years 1 month) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Education

HCMC National University expert at Multimedia graphic design, field of study · (2010 - 2012)

FPT Arena Multimedia

· (2005 - 2007)